Updating Database
	-Right click on the database project.
	-Select schema compare
	-Select source and destination on the top. Either from database to project or project to database.
	-Click compare
	-Select the objects that you want to update or add 
	(If you dont see a list of objects, check the bottom of the screen there should be a tab that says objects definitions)
	-Click update at the top